Ciaran Carson papers, circa 1970-2010
Emory University
- Arts Council of Northern Ireland records, 1973-1998, Series 9; Boxes 45-47
  - Tyrone Guthrie Center, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 15)
Johnson, Dillon 1978 August 24, TLS, 1p. 1987 May 21, ALS, 1p. 1987 July 15, ALS, 1p. CC to DJ: 1989 April 17, TLS (copy), 3pp. 1990 June 28, APC with copy of article on Tim Robinson 1991 September 24, ALS, 1p. 1992 September 30, APCS 1993 May 17, TLS, 1p. 1993 July 22, TLS, 2pp. CC to DJ: 1993 August 5, TLS (copy), 1p. 1993 November 1, TLS, 1p. 1994 January 25, TLS (copy), 1p. with calligraphic dedication of First Language [CC to DJ] 1994 August 10, TLS, 1p. 1994 December 8, ALS, 2pp. 1995 July 29, TLS, 4pp. CC to DJ: 1995 August 7, 1p. 1995 September 7, TLS, 1p. 1996 March 24, TLS, 2pp. 1996 August 11, APCS 1996 August 31, TLS, 2pp. 1997 December 16, TLS, 1p. 1998 February 13, TLS, 1p. CC to DJ: 1998 March 7, TLS, 1p. 1998 March 15, TLS, 3pp. CC to DJ: 1998 March 21, TLS, 2pp. CC to DJ 1998 April 23, TLS, 1p. 1998 June 3, TLS, 2pp. 1998 September 16, TLS, 1p. 1998 November 14, APCS 1999 August 3, TLS, 2pp.
Longley, Edna 1997 December 9, TLS, 1p.
Longley, Michael 1992 September 19, daughter Rebecca's wedding announcement undated: Christmas card to CC, with poem "Autumn Lady's Tresses" 1996 July 17, TLS, 1p. 1999 June 14, TLS, 1p. CC to ML: 1999 June 16, TLS, 1p.
McGuckian, Medbh 1976 July 13, APCS 1991 June 5, ALS (photocopy), 2pp. 1994 June 29, ALS, 2pp. undated: ALS, 8pp.
Meehan, Paula 1993 September 19, ALS with poem: "Home" [See subseries 3.1: "Home"]
Montague, John 1988 July 21, ALS, 1p.
Muldoon, Paul 1987 August, Wedding Invitation 1992 July 7, Birth Announcement with embossed poem 1995 January 28, ALS, 1p. [See Series 5: Carson and Muldoon] 1997 September 16, ALS, 1p. 1998 January 6, TLS, 1p. 1998 March 17, ALS, 1p. 1998 August 12, ALS, 1p. 1999 May 20, Birth Announcement with poem, "Cradle Song for Asher"
Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala CC to NN: 1996 July 17, TLS, 1. 1996 September 9, ALS, 1p.
O'Donoghue, Bernard 1988 March 1, TLS, 1p.
O'Faoláin, Nuala 1995 February 14, TLS, 5pp. 1996 July 17, APCS CC to NO: 1996 July17, TLS, 1p.
Olds, Sharon 1994 February, ALS 1p.
Ormsby, Frank 1972 September 30, ALS, 2pp.
Prolux, Annie 1996 May 11, ALS, 2pp. 1996 August 5, TLS, 1p. CC to AP: 1996 August 21, TLS, 1p. 1997 December 17, TLS, 1p.
Robertson, Robin CC to RR: 1995 November 30, TLS, 1p. 1995 November 31, TLS, 1p. CC to RR: 1995 December 5, TLS, 1p. CC to RR 1995 December 12, TLS, 1p.
Robinson, Tim 1995 February 11, ALS, 1p. 1995 December 14, ALS, 2pp. 1996 May 31, TLS, 1p.
Simic, Charles CC to CS: 1998 January 27, ALS, 1p.
Sommer, Piotr 1980 February 2, ALS, 2pp. 1980 April 4, ALS, 1p. 1980 May 26, ALS 4pp. 1992 December 7, ALS, 3pp. 1993 May 17, APCS 1993 June 28, ALS, 2pp. 1993 June 23, ALS, 2pp. 1993 August 20, APCS 1993 September 20, APCS 1993 December 20, APCS 1998 March 23, TLS, 1p. 1998 October 12, APCS
Tansey, Seamus 1987 July 30, TLS 2pp. 1988 April 8, TLS, 2pp.